Private High School "ParaNormal"
AM8:30  Test day
Hey, Hikaru
What
Uhh
That uhhh
What year was that battle?
Which battle
Uh, well
Dun..dun..dungeon meshi.. sorta one
Ah, right, of course!
Dan-no-ura, yeah
Dan-no-ura, 1185
Oh, by the way, yesterday...
gimme a sec
Huh?
Don't talk..!
or else I'll lose what I'm memorizing...!
Ahh. okay
Hey, Hikaru
Kuroi, you're really self-centered you know
Quiz me? With test problems?
Sure, fine
I'm saved~
Well...
Kamakura shogunate's start
Amazing
I'm not an idiot
Okay, Joukyuu rebellion
Oooh, correct
Ooh, got it
Okay, what year was Wall Maria broken through
Seriously though, stop that
Fast
Seriously, or else I'll remember manga info more than anything else
Sorry, sorry
Please, I'm begging you
Okay, the mongol invasions were what year and what year?
Ummm
The second and fourth thursday
Uh?
what was that?
That happened
The mongols invaded twice a month?
Who brought a "Recycling days chart", to class?
huh
Don't screw with me~...
No, what are you talking about?
So, my body...
it "Aborbs" right
Ah
Your black hole power huh
Right, my power's black hole, so..
Yeah
it's a relatively strong suction power
Sure
Before the test
I suck up a bunch of info
Ah, you can suck up ideas
Yeah
Not only matter and light
Oh, one sec
From this conversation, it started fading again
Uh, wa.. what are you doing?
What this'll do...
Wait you became fluent?
That' horrible~
Sorry
It'll be your fault if I fail this
I said I'm sorry
You could suck up the history text book
That was an option?
Why didn't you think of that first
I guess I was too close to see it
(lit: "lighthouse democracy", a japanese proverb reference. The light of a lighthouse can be seen from outside, not inside)
It's still dark (tn: you're an idiot, proverbally, but also black hole pun)
yabe, it's complete
You've recovered, with a power like that, the test will be easy, right
Can you use your power too Hikaru?
I can't
because my power is just to light up
Ah, I see
Don't laugh
Sorry
So don't laugh
Seriously, I can't use it
No, you can use it!
Oh?
You don't need a bike light
Not needing bike accessories is all it's good for
Huh?
There's people that move at the speed of sound, that can teleport, compared to them, that's all it does
Why is that it for me, I can just make light
Just don't laugh
Wait, it's tough (not to laugh?)
It's more tough for me
Sorry, Hikaru, you're a bit radiant, could you turn down the light a bit?
Ahh, sorry
Alex?
Shut up