Welcome
There's not a customer there you know
There's been no customers for a whole hour
so I thought I should at least say 'welcome'
I see
If we didn't do anything at all, wouldn't that be wage theft?
Don't move!
Welcome~
You don't have to say 'welcome'!
Are you not a customer?
I'm a robber.
If you looked at me you'd know that
Huh? "if I looked at you"...
Aren't you an "invisible man"?
Yes
So I can't see you...
But.. why does something feel off
The clothes, right?
Aaaah, yeah, clothes
Why are you wearing clothes?
That's weird?
Wouldn't it be better not to wear anything?...
It'd be embarassing, robbing while naked
Should an invisible man really need to feel shame like that?
What would I do if my power suddenly ran out?
I see
Certainly-
Why are you chatting with him like a friend?
He's a robber
Putting aside the invisible man stuff..
Put the money in a bag and hand it over!
You'll be charged a fee for the bag is that okay?
You don't have to follow the "customer service" manual right now!
Today was slow so there's not much money
Really? Is there any in the back room?
I wonder... Shall I call the manager to look?
Please
Boss~!
Yes?
A robber came and asked for our money...
A robber!?
Ah, an invisible man
Hand over the money!
There's a question I wanted to ask if I ever met an invisible man
What?
Do you go to public baths when you want to look at naked bodies?
.. Why the heck are you asking that?
I have the ability to stop time
Other people say "Don't you use that for pervy stuff?"
A lot of people say that, right?
I see, both abilities can be used for bad things...
You get that from strangers
TL: The phrase "tinted glasses", meaning "looking at you with a biased view", sounds very similar to "ero glasses" which is probably a porn category.
People looking at you with "erotic glasses"
it's "tinted glasses"
Have you ever actually used your power for something like that?
Is it okay if I give you a straight answer?
Of course
Not even once
That was unexpected
I thought the invisible man would never do that
Being able to use my power for pervy stuff.. I have a feeling god's testing me
I'm glad
You're glad?
I also haven't ever done such a thing.
For the same reason
I think if you used it for lust, you'd have lost
I see
Why are you crying?
Isn't it wonderful?
no, geez...
It's wrong for someone with such a strong mind to be a robber
He's right, let's stop this
Certainly...
I have enough money.
I won't rob you
I'm glad
In the end, I'll do my shopping and then go home
Please
This, please
You're gonna read a porno