Can you do that as a favor?
It's probably on top of the teacher's desk
Ah! Gotcha!
You want me to sneak into the staff room and reclaim your nintendo switch!
Hey, that loud voice...
You're "able to leave no trace", so I'm asking this favor.
There's no reason to be so loud
Ah, my bad!
But well, you having something confiscated is unusual!
It's nothing, I was playing in secret during class, and he noticed
Well, there is something embarassing..
While playing the game, I got a rare item...
Without thinking, I lit up, which is more embarassing than gaming on the sly
Huh
Did he already go? Where'd he go?
No, I'm right here!
I'm still right here!
Ah, you were still there
Stop suddenly erasing your presence
Since I really can't tell when you've erased your presence
My bad!
Anyway
If you get back my switch, I'll treat you to whatever you want
huh? Really?
Heck yeah!!
No, that's loud, too loud
You really have a real loud voice!
Anyway, think about what food you want
Well... it's about time huh..
Well, please...
... huh? Again?
Did he go... I wonder ...?
This time it definitely feels like he went... ?
Mac!!
Uwah!
Mac! Samurai Mac is good!
The broiled soy sauce double-patty one!
You startled me.... you were still there
Just now I totally thought you'd already gone
No, I wouldn't leave in the middle of a conversation, right?
I was just thinking about what I wanted to be treated to
I mean, could you not "presence erase" and then suddenly yell
It really startled me
My bad
That other time, on the train, you erased your presence..
When you gave your seat to that old person they were super startled
Aah, the old lady looked like she was about to faint
Well, it's because your loud voice startled her huh
When you offered your seat your presence was erased so wouldn't quietly leaving the seat be better
Ah, of course!
You're smart! Ahaha!
Like I said, your voice is loud
Anyway, about now there shouldn't be many teachers in the teacher's lounge
...hey, you're still there, right?
... hey, say something already
This time, it's like he really went
That guy, wasn't he just saying nonsense like "I wouldn't leave in the middle of a conversation"
Hey, teacher!
Teacher!
Please return Hikaru's Switch!
Huh, really...? The significance of presence concealment....
Yes! Excuse me!
Thank you very much!!
Switch delivery!
Just apologizing was good enough!
Right, and now samurai mac!
Well, it was a waste of the ability, but it fits you