We should be getting to sleep...
Yeah.. well, goodnight
Goodnight
Let's meet in our dreams..?
I'm glad I got a boyfriend, but..
every time we talk he gives gross vibes at the end...
Well, I guess I'll get used to it
...what the heck
A dream?
What's up with these clothes
ugh, what a corny dream
I'd never tell anyone about this
Embarassing
Having this sort of dream..
I'd never say a thing about it
I came to meet you
eh?
As promised, I came to meet you in your dream
Uwaaa
die...
eh, What's wrong?
Just now...
I was having my own gross dream, and I didn't think
eh?
Sorry
I don't think you're gross...
(sigh)
I don't really understand, but it's not your fault
You shouldn't look so down
It's my dream, so it's my fault, right?
It's definitely your dream, but me coming to meet in it is due to me
eh?
?
eh? What do you mean?
So, I came to meet you
eh? On purpose?
Yeah
eh, isn't doing that totally impossible
eh?
Don't "eh?" at me
That sorta thing deserves an "eh?"
eh? What did you mean?
I'm a guy that keeps my promises
No, I get that, but just now...
Ahh, that.. you also
No, totally impossible
Didn't you say it too?
"Meet in our dreams"
It's just a poetic phrase
eh?
"Let's meet in our dreams"
you really thought that was literal
How did you do it?
It's my power
Devil?
A prince
your prince
Really, please stop
eh, wait? You can enter other's dreams?
Not just enter
I can also see whatever dreams I want
eh?
You saw my dream yesterday about chasing rabbits
I'm glad you were having so much fun
Don't mess around with me...
eh?
Let me have a proper dream
I don't want lines that are like the opposite of Shingo Yanagisawa
I just thought you'd be glad to see me
Geez, that's enough, I'm leaving
eh?
I haven't said, but I can use "teleport"
Woah
What
Weirdly I can't use it
But of course, this is my realm after all
Give me a break!
A dream, just a dream...
Hello?
We met in our dreams
We're breaking up